[
  {
    "question": "the female client / the female clients",
    "answer": "die Kundin / die Kundinnen"
  },
  {
    "question": "France",
    "answer": "Frankreich"
  },
  {
    "question": "Monday",
    "answer": "der Montag"
  },
  {
    "question": "morning",
    "answer": "der Morgen"
  },
  {
    "question": "the message / the messages",
    "answer": "die Nachricht / die Nachrichten"
  },
  {
    "question": "the accident / the accidents",
    "answer": "der Unfall / die Unfälle"
  },
  {
    "question": "the problem / the problems",
    "answer": "das Problem / die Probleme"
  },
  {
    "question": "the help",
    "answer": "die Hilfe"
  },
  {
    "question": "the colleague / the colleagues",
    "answer": "der Kollege / die Kollegen"
  },
  {
    "question": "the solution / the solutions",
    "answer": "die Lösung / die Lösungen"
  },
  {
    "question": "the location / the locations",
    "answer": "der Standort / die Standorte"
  },
  {
    "question": "the woman / the women",
    "answer": "die Frau / die Frauen"
  },
  {
    "question": "the answer / the answers",
    "answer": "die Antwort / die Antworten"
  },
  {
    "question": "the information",
    "answer": "die Information / die Informationen"
  },
  {
    "question": "the hospital / the hospitals",
    "answer": "das Krankenhaus / die Krankenhäuser"
  },
  {
    "question": "the ambulance / the ambulances",
    "answer": "der Krankenwagen / die Krankenwagen"
  },
  {
    "question": "the call / the calls",
    "answer": "der Anruf / die Anrufe"
  },
  {
    "question": "the operation / the operations",
    "answer": "die Operation / die Operationen"
  },
  {
    "question": "the consent / the consents",
    "answer": "die Zustimmung / die Zustimmungen"
  },
  {
    "question": "the insurance / the insurances",
    "answer": "die Versicherung / die Versicherungen"
  },
  {
    "question": "the insurance office / the insurance offices",
    "answer": "das Versicherungsbüro / die Versicherungsbüros"
  },
  {
    "question": "the difficulty / the difficulties",
    "answer": "die Schwierigkeit / die Schwierigkeiten"
  },
  {
    "question": "the vacation / the vacations",
    "answer": "der Urlaub / die Urlaube"
  },
  {
    "question": "the friend (female) / the friends (female)",
    "answer": "die Freundin / die Freundinnen"
  },
  {
    "question": "big",
    "answer": "groß"
  },
  {
    "question": "to have",
    "answer": "haben"
  },
  {
    "question": "to be",
    "answer": "sein"
  },
  {
    "question": "to do / to make",
    "answer": "machen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to visit",
    "answer": "besuchen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to receive / to get",
    "answer": "bekommen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to come",
    "answer": "kommen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to speak",
    "answer": "sprechen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to need",
    "answer": "brauchen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to look for",
    "answer": "suchen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to send",
    "answer": "schicken"
  },
  {
    "question": "to answer",
    "answer": "antworten"
  },
  {
    "question": "to give",
    "answer": "geben"
  },
  {
    "question": "to call on the phone",
    "answer": "telefonieren"
  },
  {
    "question": "to organize",
    "answer": "organisieren"
  },
  {
    "question": "to drive",
    "answer": "fahren"
  },
  {
    "question": "to cost",
    "answer": "kosten"
  },
  {
    "question": "to travel",
    "answer": "reisen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to take care of / to handle",
    "answer": "erledigen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to run / to function",
    "answer": "laufen"
  }
]
